1happybirthday.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by 1HappyBirthday. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At 1HappyBirthday, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

YouTube Terms of Service : [youtube.com/static?gl=GB&template=terms](https://www.youtube.com/static?gl=GB&template=terms) Notification: Our API Client uses YouTube API Services. Google privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy> Google security settings page about revoking user access: <https://myaccount.google.com/security?pli=1>

While using 1HappyBirthday, you may see links or other references to third-party websites that may have different privacy policies. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policies of all websites you access or otherwise share your information with. Although 1HappyBirthday does enable online transactions through PayPal, 1HappyBirthday does not have access to the credit card information and therefore cannot retain or transmit or transfer your credit card information. Please visit [www.paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/) to review Paypal's privacy policy. 1HappyBirthday expressly accepts no liability or responsibility for information collected and used by any third party.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

1HappyBirthday gathers two types of information about users:  

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys:
  * Information 1HappyBirthday gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because 1HappyBirthday derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertising.

1HappyBirthday gathers User Information by The Following Processes:

We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:  

  1. Song download or registration  
We offer songs to users. 1HappyBirthday gathers the email addresses and contact information of users who voluntarily subscribe. We believe that we offer users a way to remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page.
  2. "E-mail song in the future" policy  
Our site users may choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient.
  3. Polling  
We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. 1HappyBirthday may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question.
  4. Surveys  
1HappyBirthday may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners.

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

1HappyBirthday tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. 1HappyBirthday may break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie may enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. 1HappyBirthday uses cookies to track user traffic patterns. Our advertising system may deliver a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.

1HappyBirthday uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas.  And to judge how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

1HappyBirthday uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics.

1HappyBirthday attempts to operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary. We do our best but we can not guarantee anything, so we recommend that you NEVER share sensitive information on our site or any other site.

We are currently trying to upgrade our system to give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices might include:  

  * Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.
  * Opting not to participate in song emailings.

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by 1HappyBirthday.

Read what people write about our song
